NGUYEN PHONG VU

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Contact

- **3/05/2003**
- 0784249942

learning

- vuphongnguyen030503 @gmail.com
- 32 Thuy Loi Street, Ward
 Phuoc Long A, District 9,
 HCMC
- https://github.com/phon
- https://phongvuportfolio.vercel.app/

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Tailwindcss

Javascript ,Typescript

Framework: ReactJs, NextJs

Responsive Design

State Management: Redux, Context API, Zustand

Tools: Git, Bitbucket, Jira, Git, Github, Vite, etc.

Libraries: React Hook Form , Framer Motion ,Tanstack (Query,Virtual , Router), etc.

Interests

Football

Drinks

Explore new tech

About me

I am a web developer with over 2 years of experience in React.js, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS. I've contributed to building a SaaS platform (UrSlots) focused on booking nail services, handling both front-end and back-end development.

Work Experiences

Front-end Developer

Gridly | 04/2023 - Present

- I provided ideas for frameworks and libraries for the application to replace outdated libraries, ensuring that we utilized modern and efficient technologies for better performance and maintainability.
- I built several core features of the app, such as merging branches, spell check, recording history, batch QA checks, importing localization, and facilitating real-time discussions.
- Collaborated with the backend team to ensure feature integration, troubleshoot issues, and enhance application functionality.
- Debugged and troubleshot websites, identifying and resolving any issues efficiently

Front-end/Back-end Developer

Start-up (Urslots) | 12/2023 - Present

- Helped build key features of the app, such as authentication, appointment booking, categories, services, working hours, and, most importantly, import/export for bookings, staff, and clients.
- Worked on finding and improving the UI and UX for the app, ensuring a user-friendly and visually appealing design.
- Contributed to both front-end and back-end development to build the startup app, ensuring a cohesive and functional product.

Education

Self-taught

6/2022 - 04/2023

seft-taught

- Acquired foundational knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS through self-study
- Built a personal project and learned how to deploy it, as well as use Git for version control to manage different versions of the project.

Frontend Mastery

07/2023 - 11/2023

Frontend Mastery

Course

Completed the Front End Developer course on Frontend Masters to solidify my knowledge of frontend development.

Learn on Roadmap

04/24 - 07/2024

roadmap.sh

Completed the Front End development roadmap as outlined on roadmap.sh to ensure a comprehensive understanding of frontend technologies.

Projects

Urslots Booking

12/2023 - Present

Description: **UrSlots** is a SaaS platform that streamlines nail service bookings, helping salon owners manage appointments, customer data, and schedules efficiently.

- Team: 2 developer
- Site: https://dev-merchant.urslots.com/
- Technologies: React, Tailwindcss, Typescript, Honojs, Redis, etc.

Taskify

04/2024 - 05/2024

Description: **Taskify** is a task management app inspired by Trello. It allows users to create, update, and organize tasks through an intuitive drag-and-drop interface. Taskify simplifies workflow management, making it ideal for both personal and team projects.

- Team: 1 developer
- Site: https://taskify-app-phong-vu.vercel.app/
- Technologies: Nextjs, Tailwindcss, Typescript, AivenDB, Server Action, etc.

Make Your Link

02/2024 - 03/2024

Description: Simplify your online presence with Make Your Link! Created a personalized page that allows users to showcase all their social media profiles in one place.

- Team: 1 developer
- Site: https://make-your-link.vercel.app/
- Technologies: Nextjs, Tailwindcss, Typescript, Uploadthing, etc.

Languages

English

Can communicate in English at a basic level and participate in meetings.